Jiaojiao,
do you remember who I am?
What about me?
I'm your first escort.
I just can't remember some things.
I'm not stupid.
How could I not remember you?
You left the Escort Agency without a word,
and got hurt so badly.
Grandpa was worried sick.
Is he okay?
How's the Escort Agency?
Except for no business,
everything else is fine.
Brother, let's go home and take care of you.
I can't leave yet.
I need to find out
the whole story of this fake escort mission.
Otherwise, the Agency won't get better.
I'm too slow to investigate alone.
Bai was taken away.
You can help me.
Bai Yanli?
It's good that he was caught.
If it weren't for him,
the Escort Agency wouldn't be like this.
My Lady,
are you sure he didn't take the goods?
Bai has fought with bandits
and saved my life.
It can't be him.
It's hard to say.
He has a crush on you.
What if he set up the whole thing
to play the hero?
Stop thinking about that.
You'd better take more escort missions.
Jiaojiao is right.
Don't bother with Cheng Qi.
Just focus on the escort agency.
It seems that my wife doesn't remember you.
She's still mad at me.
Feifei said
when a woman is angry, you should coax her.
Do I need to know this?
Do you have an idea?
Why are you still here?
Do you think that kick wasn't hard enough?
My dear, I was wrong.
I was wrong about everything.
I'll never make you angry again.
Who is your dear?
Are you looking for a beating?
It's me, my dear.
Who is your wife?
It's me.
Are you looking for a beating?
My lady, my lady.
Let me see you.
I am Cheng Qi.
What Cheng Qi?
I'll teach you not to talk nonsense.
Stop, stop.
Stop.
Who is your wife?
My dear,
if beating me can make you feel better,
then beat me to death.
Beat you to death?
Such a good thing,
why not leave it to me?
He will really kill me.
Jiao, save me.
Jiao,
she almost died
because of you.
I don't care what others think,
but you...
I never intended to hurt her.
Neither did I.
But you're going to divorce her.
You broke her heart.
Hello?
Can I kill someone in your yard?
As you wish.
As long as you are happy.
You just know how to dodge.
Fight me face to face.
Jiao hasn't forgiven me yet.
I can't just die like this.
Cheng Qi.
I won't let you meet her again.
He is Cheng Qi.
Save him.
Cheng Qi is not a good person.
Do you think if you kill him,
you can be with Su Yuejiao?
That's not what I thought.
You are a fugitive in the Yun State.
You and Su Yuejiao have no chance.
I can take her back to Langyue.
In Langyue, you have to be my consort.
Otherwise, your enemy won't let you go.
Your family has guarded Langyue for generations.
You are the most proud wolf.
You have the noblest blood in Langyue.
You are no longer a fugitive.
It's your responsibility to restore the glory of your family.
How do you know all this?
Because you are my man.
You wouldn't forget
our engagement, would you?
You are...
Princess?
I'll help you get back the wolf badge.
Damn it!
I almost died here.
If my father knows,
he will beat me to death.
My Lord,
isn't that the same meaning?
How could it be the same?
My father wouldn't let me die,
and neither would my wife.
But others might not be so kind.
But my lady doesn't remember you anymore.
I don't know.
It's hard to say.
Easy.
It's actually a good thing.
I did
some bad things before.
I hurt her deeply.
It's better for her to forget me
and know me again.
Are you going to be a playboy?
What if she
suddenly remembers?
You'd better
stop talking nonsense.
So,
we need to change the way.
I checked the goods before setting out.
It turned into a stone for no reason.
The problem
should be found from the person who sent the goods.
This is the border between the Yun State and the Langyue State.
Since you are asked to deliver the goods here,
the person is likely to be in the city.
Do you remember what he looks like?
Let's split up and look for him.
I don't remember clearly.
But I might remember if I see him.
I just remember he has a big beard.
Mr. Su,
how dare you come here?
I'm here
to ask you to take a mission.
I'm sorry.
We don't take missions now.
I heard that you never refuse any order.
Is that a rumor?
I'll go and clarify it.
What kind of escort
do you want?
I broke my leg recently.
I need escorts to accompany me to go shopping.
I need three escorts.
You must be there.
Here's the deposit.
Then tomorrow at dawn,
we'll be waiting.
Farewell.
Will he even get up that early?
There are so many weirdos in this city.
Tomorrow, while accompanying him,
we'll split up and inquire
about the whereabouts of that Lang Yue.
My Lord,
why must we leave so early?
Getting up early shows diligence.
But you look so sleepy.
Lady Shen is not blind.
I'm not sleepy.
I'm full of energy.
I'll follow him to the market.
You two go to the courier station and the escort team.
If you encounter them, don't fight.
If there's no news,
meet at the rouge shop at the end of the street.
Go shopping with me.
No.
Su Yuejiao can go shopping with Cheng Qi.
Why can't you go with me?
Go.
You can't go out like this.
Change him.
Yes.
What are you doing?
Stop, stop.
No, stop, no, stop.
I'll do it myself.
Zhalu.
No, no, no.
Excuse me, have you seen a bearded merchant from Langyue?
There are many bearded merchants from Langyue.
It's hard to find the one you want.
What are you looking for?
Just asking.
Don't worry, I won't waste your time.
If you want to buy something,
just tell me.
You can buy
whenever you want.
How about
I help you find him?
You can get your money back
if you don't want to go on.
The escort fee can be returned to you at a discount.
I'd rather go shopping.
By the way,
this blanket
is of good quality.
I believe you must like it.
It's for you.
I don't like it.
This is a specialty of Langyue Lake.
Young man, don't you think so?
No.
Just take it.
Young man, except this,
what other specialties does this city have?
There's no errand today.
Although they are divorced,
but
I should still give them
the final episode.
Don't be so upset.
Cheng Jiao's story is far from over.
Is it really okay
to let her take those things?
She's a bodyguard after all.
And those things are all for her.
It's okay.
My Lord, stop buying.
We don't have much money left.
Don't you have private money?
Use your money first.
I'll pay you back later.
Let's go.
Boss
Two bags of chestnuts, please.
Okay.
Thank you.
Ms. Su
This is really delicious.
Try it.
Let's go.
Turn around and see if she's eaten it.
Yes, she has.
Really?
Excuse me,
I'd like to know
if your shop has business dealings with Yunjing.
Our main store is indeed in Yunjing,
but the rouge is from Pingjiang.
The rouge from Pingjiang, the powder from Guangling.
Why do you suddenly use rouge?
What?
The rouge from Pingjiang, the powder from Guangling.
Someone told me.
You are an expert.
Is your boss from Langyue?
Or has any business dealings with Langyue?
This is a shop in the Yun State.
The boss surnamed Zhang.
There are many customers from Langyue.
How about this?
I'll
draw the person you're looking for.
You've seen a lot of people.
Maybe you'll remember him after seeing this.
Could you please lend me a pen and paper?
How about it?
It should be.
I can't remember clearly.
What about the shopkeeper?
Do you have any impression?
No.
I remember.
He wore a brown agate bead string
on his left wrist.
Agate bead string.
This time,
I'll ask the painter to draw a few more.
I'll look for him with the portrait.
I don't believe
no one in the whole city has seen him.
I've said
I'll take care of finding him.
I didn't expect it to be quite exotic.
You really have a good taste.
Princess.
Except for Langyue,
have you ever seen
such a pompous woman in the Yun State?
Who painted this?
Princess, do you know this person?
Yes.
I can find him.
He likes beautiful women and good wine,
and likes the poetry of Cheng Qi.
Beautiful women, good wine, and you,
he will definitely appear.
Miss,
there's news about Cheng Qi.
He has returned to Yunjing.
He will perform poetry at a banquet in the city of Klax.
Who set the banquet?
It seems to be the princess of Langyue.
No wonder there's an extra Xiangyue Tower
and frequent purchases of poetry books.
It turns out he met a noble.
Should we
send someone to keep an eye on him?
Forget it.
Since he's still writing poetry,
he'll come across her sooner or later.
After everyone is seated,
this can be the stage for the speech.
As for the seating,
the emperor's son-in-law and I will sit here.
You and Mr. Su will sit here.
That's good.
It's more convenient for me to get up and give a speech.
Actually, you don't have to bother.
Just tell me
his name
or how to find him.
His name is Arsal.
He is a very powerful businessman in Langyue.
No one knows where he is.
But I'm sure
if he knows that Cheng Qi is coming to the banquet,
he will definitely appear.
I'm worried that if we don't get along,
it may disturb the banquet.
It doesn't matter.
No one can hurt you in my place.
I will protect you.
Princess,
I've always been curious
why you're so nice to me.
This is your love story,
and it's where I fell in love with you.
You can recall it.
Anyway,
thank you, Princess.
I'll try my best
not to ruin Xiangyue Tower.
Mr. Su,
I'll take my leave now.
Princess.
I have to keep this painting.
I'll give it to my wife.
I'm sorry to make you suffer.
But
you look heroic in the portrait.
You're a hero.
For Langyue,
it doesn't matter.
You're right.
Yikeba colluded with Yunjing.
As long as it's not escorted by the Fuyun Escort Agency,
it will be robbed by his men.
As expected.
But I told you
to protect Su Yuejiao after the order.
How did she get hurt?
We followed her out of Yunjing.
But the emperor's son-in-law appeared halfway.
We can't get too close to them,
and can't let the robbers recognize us.
Finally, we came up with a way to lure them away.
Forget it.
They are made for each other.
Even if they forget,
they will fall in love again.
How did Yikeba react
when he knew I would hold a banquet
for Cheng Qi?
He's a little soft.
He just mocked the Princess a little.
Find a way to get him to the banquet.
I want him to see
how I do for Cheng Qi.
Should I avoid him?
No.
It's time for him
to meet an old friend.
Yes, Your Highness.
Wait.
Don't you like reading scripts?
I think Gong Xi writes well.
My brother and Fachaibo
have told me about us.
I...
I don't really want to divorce you.
It's to save the Escort Agency.
Right?
I know it's not the reason.
It's because of what I said at the Grand Preceptor's Villa
hurt your feelings.
But
if I didn't say that,
Zhang Xi Yun would definitely do something bad to you.
Fortunately, everything is fine now.
Mr. Cheng,
I don't remember some things.
Whatever we had before,
I just want to guard the Escort Agency.
Then I'll guard it with you,
just like before.
Mr. Cheng,
you're involved in too much trouble.
I don't want the Agency to suffer with you.
Thank you for painting for me.
From now on, we're just employer and employee.
You give me the order,
and I'll give you a discount.
Thank you.
Sign here.
Mr. Cheng, please sign for me.
It's my turn.
I want one, too.
I didn't expect Cheng Qi
to be so popular in the city of Klara.
I should bring some of Gong Xi's words next time.
Good idea.
Thank you.
Cheng Qi is really talented.
Let him go like this,
don't you feel it's a pity?
I run a escort agency.
It's more important to know martial arts.
You've always thought that?
Then why did you fall in love with him before?
Is it because he's handsome?
Princess,
if you like him, just do it.
Don't force us together.
It seems that your method
is not very effective.
I want her to see that many people like you.
She doesn't like poetry.
You really know her.
By the way,
why is there no bookstore here?
The books they hold are all different.
It's a mess.
Those books were smuggled from Yunjing.
They are in short supply.
So many people can't buy them.
They can only copy and print them by themselves.
If we can trade,
your books will be sold well
here and in
Langyue.
Father,
Ling Feng has finished the work.
Good job.
Establish your authority slowly,
and you'll be ready for the future.
Father,
there's something I've been confused about.
You want to know
why the Star Conference didn't let you take over directly.
You really can't hide anything from you.
Not just the Star Conference,
but also the shops with money transactions.
Why are they all given to that girl?
To achieve great things, one must know how to use others.
If you take the lead,
who will cover for you
if something goes wrong?
But...
Everything in the Zhang family will be yours in the future.
I must plan well for you.
As for you,
just collect profits with clean hands.
No need to get your hands dirty.
Leave the dirty work
to someone else.
Alright.
I understand.
Good.
I don't drink
wine.
This
is specially prepared for you.
Langyue's grape juice.
Don't worry.
My Lord.
It seems that the idea of the Princess
to find the people of Langyue is not feasible.
If we can't even find the Princess,
we'd better go back quickly.
I'm worried that my grandfather
is annoyed by my uncle.
It's been a long time since the house was so quiet.
I miss My Lord.
I want to make a fortune.
All you know is eating.
You're always eating.
Aren't you worried?
Their kong fu is better than mine.
I can't do anything about it.
Since they're fine,
they'll come back to eat with me sooner or later.
I should eat more.
Right, dad?
Go ahead.
Clouds cross the desert, sky is vast.
Wine overflows, banquet is warm.
Deep gratitude for the journey.
Mountains and rivers, all are joyful.
It's him!
I'll kill him!
As a warrior of Lang Yue,
you need to be brave and strategic.
Stay calm.
I have a plan.
Princess,
you have a new favorite.
Didn't you like
the writer from the Yun State?
General,
he is
the top poet of the Yun State,
the poet you like.
Are you Cheng Qi?
Yes, I am.
But I have stepped down from the top spot.
I just like writing poems.
What are you saying?
Take him away.
Yes, yes.
What are you doing?
Princess likes him.
I'll help Princess
bring him to Langyue.
This is the border city of the Yun State.
I'm also a citizen of the Yun State.
Please be careful.
Yikeba,
I invited you here to drink,
not to cause trouble.
You've ruined my good mood.
Don't be angry.
The general prepared beautiful women
and good wine for you to make you happy.
If you want to use it, just sit down.
Thank you for protecting me.
I...
I didn't do that for you.
You're from Yun State.
You can't be bullied by Langyue people.
Yes, yes, yes.
You're right.
Your Majesty,
the amount of construction in and around
Kala Town and Yunjing has suddenly increased,
and the treasury has been depleted.
At the same time,
the prices in these places have also risen.
Merchants have raised prices,
but the wages of the people
remain unchanged.
But no one
mentioned these in the court today.
Do you think
someone did it on purpose?
I think
they can't wait
to reap the benefits.
It's not just this.
Look at
Ling Feng's speech
is smooth
and well-structured.
I'm waiting for that...
But...
But it's just a pile of words
with no real content.
This speech
is quite different from his previous ones.
But to me,
it resembles Mr. Ling's style.
You're eager to make Ling Feng stand out.
Cheng Qi,
how long until we return to Yunjing?
The report says
Cheng Qi is writing for the actress at Xiangyue Tower.
He'll return to the capital in a few days.
He started performing early.
Then I need to hurry up.
I'll get on it right away.
I don't know if he and Su Yuejiao
have made up.
If I want to catch him,
I don't need you to do it.
Writing lyrics needs a quiet place.
You don't understand at all.
I don't understand.
For him,
you're going to trade.
These people from Yun State are very bad.
They want our cattle, sheep and gems.
You have so many cattle and gems,
but you don't know how to enjoy them.
Is the wine in Yunjing
better than that in Langyue?
Everything you like
can be found in the city of Kla.
I don't care.
I just want to be the first to read
Cheng Qi's books and poems.
If you don't agree to trade,
you have to find another way.
Then we can find a fast courier agency
to deliver the books for you.